# Andrew Millikin

Knowledge in developing Responsive & Interactive websites/Knowledge in CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap, and React JS/Very good knowledge of AMP, JavaScript, and JQuery

Kelowna, BC V1W4A2 ahmillikin@gmail.com +1 604 600 8600

Learning these languages and frameworks has been a very enjoyable challenge, I am a sponge for new information and seek out new information and better ways to enhance my projects.

Learning using outdated courses has encouraged me to do my own research for best practices and how to work around outdated packages.

#### Personal Details

#### Highest Level of Education: Secondary School

# Work Experience

#### **Drummer**

Swear Jar - Western Canada May 2018 to Present

I compose, record, and perform music with a solid group of friends.

#### **Drummer**

Parting Ways - Western Canada May 2015 to Present

I compose, record, and perform music with a solid group of friends.

#### **Drummer**

Hold the Line - Western Canada January 2014 to Present

I compose, record, and perform music with a solid group of friends.

#### **Fiber Optic Technician**

Harbourview Electric - Burnaby, BC June 2016 to March 2020

Placed and spliced fiber optics all across the Lower Mainland including Squamish and Whistler. Build Splice cases, tested splices with Shaw, connected new building with fiber, and updated old building from coax to fiber for better service.

#### **Drummer**

Youth Fountain - Western Canada March 2017 to October 2019 I compose, record, and perform music with a solid group of friends.

#### **Carpenter Apprentice**

Sea-Pat Construction - North Vancouver, BC April 2014 to June 2016

Demolished and built homes from the ground up as well as updated/renovated older homes. Concrete foundations, footings, framing, finishing, roofing. Comfortable using hand tools, and learning new techniques and practices quickly.

#### **Technical Support Representative**

Shaw Communications - Vancouver, BC July 2012 to April 2014

Inbound call center agent responsible for technical difficulties. Learned how to navigate their old DOS system to optimize work performance. Received inbound calls to extend help with technical issues regarding internet, phone, television, and billing.

Upgraded everyone in the Lower Mainland to the new system (requiring everyone to have a Shaw/Telus box). Upgraded packages with discounts, and helped retain business.

Ensured customers had a positive experience as well as fixed any issues they may have been experiencing, as well as offer them cheap package upgrades.

#### Education

# Secondary School in Web, Blockchain, Video Game Development

Udemy - Kelowna, BC

February 2021 to Present

#### Skills

- Bucket Truck Experience
- Construction
- Telecommunication
- · Troubleshooting
- Computer Networking
- Cabling
- React
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Node.js
- Python
- Visual Studio
- Unity

- C#
- Redux
- Django
- Kotlin
- Bootstrap
- GitHub
- Flask
- jQuery
- Splicing
- Solidity
- Truffle/Ganache
- MetaMask
- Ethereum
- C++
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Shopify
- Application Development
- User Interface (UI)
- Java
- AWS
- APIs
- Microsoft SQL Server
- MySQL
- Visual Studio

## Links

http://Haydn-king.github.io

https://eth-marketplace-course.vercel.app/

https://github.com/Haydn-King

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-millikin-669262220/

# Certifications and Licenses

# **Build a Blockchain and Cryptocurrency**

August 2021 to Present

Build and deploy a blockchain and cryptocurrency using Python, JS, and React.

# **Build an app with React, Redux and Firestore**

September 2021 to Present

Build an app with React, Redux, and Firestore from scratch.

## Blockchain A-Z Learn How to Build your First Blockchain

March 2021 to Present

Learned about how Blockchain's interact and how to develop my own.

# **Build your own Proof of Stake Blockchain**

July 2021 to Present

Using Python and Visual Studio, we learned to develop and test our own Proof of Stake Blockchain

# **The Complete Android 11 Developer Course**

March 2021 to Present

Learned how to build and developed different types of apps using Android Studio.

# **Ethereum Blockchain Developer Bootcamp with Solidity**

March 2021 to Present

Using Truffle/Ganache, MetaMask, and the Ethereum platform Solidity to develop smart contracts and Dapps on the Ethereum Network.

#### Beginner's Guide to Responsive Web Design with Flask

June 2021 to Present

Learned how to develop responsive websites using Flask.

# The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

January 2021 to Present

Learned the fundamentals of digital marketing, including SEO.

#### **Master Ethereum and Solidity Programming**

June 2021 to Present

Learned how to develop smart contracts on the Ethereum Network.

#### **Lean Six Sigma White Belt**

March 2021 to Present

Learned guidelines, basic concepts, and best practices of Sigma Six.

#### **Portfolio Website**

June 2021 to Present

Learned how to develop a portfolio website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with Hosting.

#### **React - The Complete Guide**

September 2021 to Present

Learned about best practices and implementations of the React Framework, including Hooks, React Router, and Redux.

#### **Build Modern Responsive Website**

March 2021 to Present

Learned how to build and develop a modern responsive website using HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap.

# **Shopify Dropshipping**

April 2021 to Present

Learned how to navigate through Shopify and build my own e-commerce dropshipping platform. Learning best practices and how to build customers using ads, email marketing, and discount codes.

## **Developing Smart Contracts with Solidity**

June 2021 to Present

Learned how to develop and test smart contracts using Solidity on the Ethereum Network using test networks.

## **Unity Game Development**

May 2021 to Present

Learned how to develop an RPG Adventure game using Unity and C#. Learned how to navigate and integrate Unity with Visual Studio's, and created a fully functioning game.

# Additional Information

I'm a self-taught drummer who has proven that you don't need a formal education to exceed in life. During and after high school I joined the work force when I was 13 years old. I started off at a bakery making \$7 an hour, and used that money to finance my very own drum set.

I am extremely motivated and work well with others. My passion for creativity and perfection carries over into every aspect of my life. I am capable of learning new advanced concepts, and know how to conduct my own research and development without supervision.

I love to both teach others what I know, and learn new concepts, best practices, and efficiency. I look forward to working with you in the future.